Good evening!
Morning chime has sounded
We are Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku. Sakuragi Cocona and Hoshina Mirei.
Let's do it.
It's been a while.
Before we start the show, we will decide who will be the MC.
Please vote for the one you like.
The person with the number on the card is today's MC.
Let's start the voting.
Which one has which one?
It's a gal party.
And her hair color is amazing.
It's pink.
Pink is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
But I'm sure I dye my hair tomorrow.
What color do you want?
Blue.
No, I don't want blue.
No blue.
Okay.
Until the voting is over.
5,4,3,2,1.
Okay.
Which one?
Ready, Ta-da! Oh, then it's cocona for today.
Yes, so I'm MC of today, which I have the number 2.
Thank you.
Yes, so,
No, I can't take this anymore.
I'll take it.
Let's start.
Ebi-chu's
Ebi-chu's Happy and Fufu's showroom.
Today is the 72nd time.
Thank you for watching Ebi-chu's Happy and Fufu's showroom.
Ebi-chu's Happy and Fufu's showroom is
a show that is like a sister to Ukka's showroom.
So, it's time to spread the word.
Yes.
What should I do?
To have more people watch this live, we will announce on the official X of Ebi-chu.
Please spread the word.
Please.
I'll call the manager.
Yes.
What should I do? What manager to do it. What's good?
What's good?
It's a bit laggy.
Gyalpi! Gyalpi!
Okay! Please spread the word!
Please spread the word!
I think it's going to be Morc!
Isn't Morc's pose too difficult?
What do you think about it?
This is the only one I have.
Simple.
So, today we are going to do this.
It's called,
Fun and Fufu's survey talk.
That's right.
It's a survey talk where you take a survey before you talk and decide what to talk about.
This is it first one.
Please vote which you are most interested in.
Please read it.
1. FAMIE 2024 Report 2. TIFF 2024
3. Ebi-Chu Summer Festival
4. 15th Anniversary Tour Tokyo & Osaka
5. World Championships
6. How to enjoy when you are sad
7. Gyal-Kaiwa
I'm curious about everything.
I think you are curious about everything.
Please start. Start!
The first one.
I'm curious about everything.
I think I can do it all.
Then, let's see.
It's about time.
Finished!
Let's see the result.
You are so cool.
The first place is Gyal-Kaiwa of the number 7.
I think it's a little too much.
Do you want to be the first place?
There's something that's over.
I think it's a little too much.
She's getting angry.
The Gyal-Kaiwa is starting.
Seriously.
This is the last place.
That's right. That's right, everyone.
What?
What's wrong?
You can say that you're going to raise it here.
I don't know what to talk about.
That's right.
It's like talking like a gyaru.
I'm a gyaru sister.
That's right.
Then, something.
Shall we do it? Let's try to talk like a girl group.
Here we go.
Yay! Mireia-chan again!
It's been a while since we last met. What were you doing?
I was sleeping in the bathroom.
I didn't come at all. I was in the bathroom.
I was in the bed and I was in bed all the time and I was pien.
I really want to quit as soon as possible, but do you have any questions?
Do you have any questions?
How is it?
I can't see you responding.
Is pien over?
Maybe it's a Heisei era.
Heisei gal.
So we are Heisei gal?
We are Heisei gal?
Heisei gal is popular now.
What's wrong?
Did you go back to Ibaraki?
Ibaraki?
Ibaraki is very popular.
I went to Ibaraki. Ibaraki is really popular. I've been to Ibaraki too many times.
I've been there too many times.
The last one is Gyalcon.
I'm really not used to Gyalcon.
I just woke up Gyalcon.
That's why Ibaraki is popular.
It's really popular.
Do you have any? I don't know.
I don't have a summer vacation.
Hurry up and do it.
I'll get angry.
I'm not old enough to use that word.
I'm not old enough to use that word. I'm not old enough to use that word. I'm not old enough to use that word. I'm not old enough to use that word. I'm not old enough to use that word. Isn't it already? This is also old. Gekigokopunpunmaru
Gekigokopunpunmaru is my high school days.
I'm embarrassed.
It's a very closed character.
I wonder if it's stopped.
I wonder what the character is saying now.
What do you do after the summer break? We suddenly got bored.
Like autumn?
We got bored.
We posted that everyone had finished their summer vacation.
I thought our summer had started.
It started recently.
It's like a late summer vacation.
Where did you go? Where did you go?
Why are you so quiet?
I can't do this.
I'm a girl.
You slept too much in Ibaraki.
I've come to feel it naturally.
I'm a business girl.
Business girl?
Yuno is doing business with BAB.
Now?
Is that what you mean by business girl?
Yes.
It's over.
This is the last one. You know, right?
Let's move on. What's next?
Start!
Ready? Start!
I've been a businesswoman since I joined.
Stop it!
Stop saying that!
But you guys like that, right?
You're so stubborn.
That's right.
Shall we start?
Yes!
Finished!
Hami-en, the 2024 report meeting.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming this year.
This year is the time of Obon.
I'm serious.
The typhoon was scary.
On the way back, it was a heavy traffic jam.
I think everyone was stuck in traffic jams on the way home.
How was it?
But thanks to the typhoon, both days were good.
It was good that there that the weather was good.
There are some pictures.
Can you see them?
Let's see.
There was no sakura coconut.
So we took pictures with Ucchi.
Ucchi-san was there too!
I was so happy. When I got it from Nonoka, I cried.
My parents brought me a water bottle.
There was no coconut, so I only brought a watermelon.
I thought there was a coconut inside.
It was red inside.
Thank you.
Thank you. It was delicious.
I ate watermelon.
That was my soul.
Let's move on.
This is the first day's costume.
This year's costume is different from the first day's outfit was different.
This is cute.
This is...
This is not fitted yet.
What?
Did you wear it?
I did.
That's good.
I wanted to wear it.
It was really cute.
The red one.
It was cute.
I think I'll wear this in a costume for a live performance.
Please look forward to it.
This is a fairy costume.
It's not a butterfly costume.
It's a costume that says the butterfly came to the fairy.
But this fabric is heavy when it's wet.
It dries quickly, it's pretty cold.
This is really cute.
The member color is cute.
Everyone is wet.
Next.
This is Yasushi.
Aya-chan's bangs are too bad.
It's stable. Aya-chan's bangs are too bad. It was the first day, but the second day was the first song that we were really caught.
But it was this from the beginning.
Is this the first one?
This is the second day, so it's different, but the first day was like this.
It's terrible.
This is like a default. But this year, water was on everyone, so I told everyone not to do it.
The fans, the family, said,
I don't want to do it anymore!
The mission and the hot-up at this time were really good, so I said,
I don't want to do it, stop it!
I was sorry, but I was doing, I'm sorry. I was sorry.
I was sorry.
It's an event.
Let's move on.
It's so nice.
It's so sunny.
It's the second day.
It's so beautiful.
It's hot.
We have a stage roof.
It was a very hot state of ecstasy.
It was hot.
It was hot, so the cold things were sold out.
Then, on this day, the water was very dry.
It was very hot without water on the center stage. I see.
It was so hot.
I burned my wristband.
It was just right to be wet.
I see.
It's better than rain.
Thank you for your rice balls.
This year, it's a set with tonjiru.
Isn't it the best?
Most of the members ate it for breakfast.
Thank you.
I want to eat that.
I want to improve my cooking.
I want to be more loyal to my rice balls.
You released it last year.
I released it for 3 years.
I want to be more loyal to my rice balls.
Thank you.
That's great.
Let's move on.
This is the center stage.
Oh, I can definitely dance.
This is the dance.
The new song, FAMILY ENDING, is called
IROHANI ODORE ANSE.
This song is about throwing a towel. It's a chorus. Actually, I'm doing a dance that I throw.
It's a chorus.
I asked for a dance, and it's a little bit too much to turn.
It's a little too much to turn, so I asked for a different feeling.
As a result, it became like this.
Is this okay?
Isn't it taken by people?
Everyone may be taking this by someone,
but it was quite difficult to go to various places depending on the wind.
What I wanted to refer to in this picture was
Mr. Eikichi Yazawa.
Yes.
A teacher who pretended to have seen Mr. I had seen this before. I was told that I should go to the towel song.
I was told that I should go to the towel song.
I've never seen a towel in Yazawa Ekichi.
I'll give it to you all.
I see.
I think there are people of my generation.
I got it from a-chan.
A-chan is here.
I got the reference from Ikichi Yadawa.
Please try it.
It's good.
It's easy to do.
You just raise the right and left and jump.
I jump up and down.
Please try it.
There is a live performance in summer.
I will do it again.
Please remember the summer. Please remember my dance moves.
Next.
I saw fireworks.
It's beautiful.
But...
What is this?
It's fireworks.
But it's too bright.
It's night, right?
It's a night hair.
But it's too bright.
It's too bright. Not too bright?
Was the opening time a little early this year?
It's a 16 o'clock opening, but I was in charge of the last song.
Yes.
The last one was Blue Dijoness.
Encore, right?
Wait, wait.
No, isn't it bright?
It's bright.
Wait.
No, can I say the last song?
Did you?
It was brighter than this.
I said, sorry, but isn't it bright?
Can you see the fireworks?
You said it.
I didn't say fireworks, but I asked if it was okay.
I forgot to say it.
Everyone knows that fireworks are at the end of the screen. I think it would be better if it was a little darker.
I think it's a little wasteful, but it's rare.
I think it's rare.
I think it's rare. Kobayashi Kaho did the rap part of COCO NUNNAN. I did say that. He said,
I want to go to the foot of the mountain.
He always did the KUSHIN.
It's not KUSHIN.
KUSHIN.
Please don't say KUSHIN.
He always did KUSHIN.
He said,
I will do it.
Kobayashi Kaho will do KUSHIN to our request.
Wasn't there a lot of KUSHIN?
He did it from the beginning.
He said, I will do it. He did a lot of self-reflection? You were doing it from the beginning. I was trying to do it.
I was told that I should never do it.
Self-reflection.
I was the one who did the rap.
I was like, wait a minute.
I want to do it.
And you did it on the real show.
I was watching the real show.
I was looking at the face. Everyone was watching. Everyone was laughing.
Everyone was laughing.
That was the most interesting part.
That was interesting.
Another picture?
This is the picture.
There's more.
Let's go to the next one.
This is the second day's outfit.
It's cute. It's cute.
The marine costume was cute.
The marine costume is cute.
Yes.
There is also a hat.
As a result of the water-drenched hat, it was okay to wear a lot of water.
Wow!
It's amazing.
I was able to respond.
I was saying, I will never stop wearing this hat.
It's wet and it falls on my hair. It's cute, but it's falling on my hair.
It's cute but delicious. There are still many photos.
It's so easy to get a belly.
That's right.
Yuno did abalone bone-out instead of coconut.
She did it for me.
Abalone bone-out.
Let's see the next photo.
This is the center stage of the afternoon.
It's so cute.
From the first song, it's all wet.
Oh, you got wet.
The second one too.
It's so cute.
Thanks to the water, everyone was alive and well.
They're alive.
They're all alive. You were alive. You were alive.
I was alive.
Let's move on.
The second day, I was allowed to use all the water left.
I was so full.
I thought I was going to drown.
That much?
I was crouching on the couch.
It was so bad.
I thought I was going to drown.
We were like...
We had 10 times of famine.
We were like, oh my god.
This year was the first time?
I don't know. The amount of water was strange.
I thought I could go that far.
I felt tired after the pool.
There are still pictures.
Next.
Good smile.
I did a rental competition.
This is the last picture.
Cute.
I tried to do a rental competition at the family party.
I was a little bit nervous.
But I didn't really get into it.
I wanted to make it a song that would leave a good impression on everyone.
I wanted to make it a good memory.
I didn't have a flower path, so I could go to many places.
So I competed for the prize.
The second topic was about the person who had a Femmian towel in 2014 and the team who was looking for sun oil.
There was no sun oil. I was in the same team as Emma.
Everyone had sun oil because they had to stop their sunburn.
There are not many people who use sun oil.
There are not many.
But miraculously, one man had it.
He had it.
It was burned beautifully.
Nice.
I was really impressed.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
That's right.
That's it for this year's Hami-e.
Thank you very much. It was really fun.
Thank you very much.
This was fun.
I'm looking forward to what kind of outfit it is.
I'm really looking forward to it.
That's all.
Hami-e is over.
Next.
Start.
Maya is the first to ride a bicycle.
Maya said it's okay.
Bicycle.
Maya was riding a bicycle with a lot of energy.
Yes. Which one? Maya was riding a bicycle with a lot of energy. Yes, yes.
Which one?
Oh, number 3. Yubi-chan, summer festival.
Wow, it's a very distant memory.
That's right, in Shinjuku.
Yes, on August 4th at Shinjuku Pepe-san. It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a new song.
It's a new song.
It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a new song. It's a Yukata.
It was really fresh to do a live there. I was so happy to see the place where we usually go to.
I was so happy to see so many people.
We talked a lot while we were moving.
I was wearing a Yukata, but I moved to other places.
I feel like I became a Disney Princess.
I agree.
I want to wear a dress next time.
I think I've never been a real Disney Princess.
Let's do it. Princess? Oh, I didn't know that.
Shall we try? Let's do it.
What was your feeling when you watched the live from above?
Yes, I watched the live from above.
I watched the live from above.
But I think there were a lot of people.
And the foreign people were also...
Oh, that's true.
It's really...
Oh, it's not related to the priority area. I don't excited. I don't know if it's related to the priority area.
They came in more and more and had a lot of fun together.
I was surprised.
I took a video of the dance.
I took a video of the dance on the day of the video.
Yes.
We weren't the water team, right? Oh, I was on top.
I wanted to pour water on everyone.
I wanted to do it too.
I wanted to practice side by side.
The general public stopped me.
I wonder what they are doing.
We don't have many opportunities to do anniversary events like this. So we decided to do it this year.
And that's the plan.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Shall we move on?
Yes.
Start!
I want you to throw the rice cake. What do you mean?
It must hurt.
Yes! Yes, it's done!
Oh, number 5!
What is it?
Yes, I...
After the fan meeting, what did I do?
I participated in the world tournament.
What kind of world tournament?
I participated in the world Championships. What kind of World Championships? I participated in the World Championships in Morcque.
How was it?
I lost 5 to 1.
You lost a lot.
I participated in the Star Dust Morcque and Star Morcque.
I won the championship to practice after I was born.
I thought, really?
It was a world competition.
I practiced once during the rehearsal period.
I thought, really?
After that, the schedule didn't match.
I practiced at Hakodate.
At the world tournament.
I was the only one who didn't make it.
When you made it?
I lost all the tournaments.
And when I wasn't there,
I heard that a French player was playing.
Oh, I see.
I thought it was impossible.
My members said so.
Did you succeed in the practice?
Everyone's performance is very good.
Oh, I see.
They are doing it very well.
But there are people who are participating in the world championships who are practicing a lot.
And there are people who are working as a team.
And there are kids and family members.
And there are different teams in Mork.
There are kids and 4 people who are working together.
There are people who are participating in of the group. If there are more than 4 members, it's okay. There are 4 members.
There are some members who will be on the group.
I asked them what kind of flow they were in.
They said, there is a world competition.
They asked me if I would join the group.
I said yes.
I said I would join.
They said I was the leader.
I was the leader.
From now on,
I will be good at practicing. we will be better.
We want to make more fun of Mork.
We are trying to practice a lot to be able to participate in the tournament.
Really?
We can buy Mork set for 7,000 yen. It's easy to make.
I've been doing Mork for a year and a half.
You did it before.
I saw it and asked if it was Mork.
And Morita from the youth Hikari is also part of the team called King of Mork. King Mork is very famous in the Mork community.
And we will have a 2 man live show next time.
I thought I should say hello, but the venue is different.
We can't meet.
That's right.
With Morita-san, someday...
Morita Miraihai...
I want to see it!
I want to gather with everyone in the morning.
That's the best.
I want you to teach me how to throw.
I'll do my best to get better.
I want you to win.
There are many teams.
There are people who are doing competitions.
I want you to talk to us about the tournament.
I'll do my best.
Let's do one more!
It was a Japanese team that won Japanese team. Amazing. Amazing, right?
Next.
Number 6.
What?
How to enjoy when you're sad.
I think you're curious about this.
Do you have any stories when you're sad?
I have a lot.
I was sad every day for a while.
I was wondering if it was true. Is that so? Do you have any sad stories? I have a lot. I have one every day.
I was wondering if it was true.
I'm the type who can tell the story.
I see.
I have one sad story.
Is that so?
I'm in the same situation.
What do you mean?
I come here almost every day.
How do you enjoy it?
I think it's good to play with it in your head.
What do you mean?
You know you will come, right?
At that time, please open your eyes without closing them.
If you open them, you will find something.
Really?
You will find something.
You can get along with that if you do your best. I think it's better not to get along with someone if you try hard.
I think you should never get along with someone.
I want to join it.
First of all, it's important not to be scared.
I want you to open your eyes.
I can't open my eyes.
Really?
I opened my eyes.
I was opened.
Isn't it amazing? I was opened. Who was it opened it. She opened it. Isn't that amazing?
And she was there.
Who was she?
Someone who looked like me.
Scary.
She looked like me but I didn't have eyes so I was a little scared.
But...
Are you okay? You're not wearing underwear?
I'm not wearing underwear.
You're not wearing underwear.
I'm not panty. You're not panty. I'm embarrassed.
But I took a deep deep breath and I felt that I could get it if I relaxed my body.
And I thought you were noisy.
You were like,
I thought you were noisy.
You said, I'm sleeping, so let me sleep.
I thought you were going to cut me off., you're sleeping, so let me sleep. I was like, you're sleeping, so let me sleep.
I was like, you're sleeping, so let me sleep.
That's amazing.
Isn't it scary?
I'm scared.
I sometimes hear a snoring.
I sometimes hear's snoring.
I thought, maybe they are sleeping together.
I think it's important to be close to them.
Let's go to the bathroom.
It's summer.
It's a scary story.
Let's go.
Last! Start!
Is it over? Last! Start!
Is there really someone?
I don't like it.
But I confirmed it myself.
There was no one.
Finished. Number 2! I'm done. The second one. Tiff. Tiff.
I miss her.
I was so hot.
I can't stop.
This time, we had a live with a song called Anemone in Motomen.
And a live with Ebichu.
Ebichu has been on the show three times. We had 3 shows in which we had to separate from the other members.
How was it?
The first song was a big hit. When Nonoko and I first started the song,
everyone noticed the moment we left the mic.
We didn't do it that often, but they noticed it so quickly.
It was like...
It was like... It was like... It was amazing. Everyone was doing nostalgic songs.
Yes, almost all of them were nostalgic songs.
This time, I wanted to do it with Ema Yuna and Nono.
So I took that opinion and it was all old songs.
I see.
That's right.
It was all a long time ago. That's right. It was really fun.
It's a fresh feeling that the fans of the old days have in their hearts.
That's right.
I think it's an emotional feeling.
And the costumes are the same.
The yellow and blue costumes of the PAMIEN of the Onee-san members.
I wore that.
It was very emotional.
It was very exciting.
I thought it was the end of the year.
It was hot.
It was hot. It was a. It was a hot day.
I don't remember the second half.
I forgot.
What about the other members?
We looked at the list of the members and thought about what to this. I got a shrimp-cutting.
I got a shrimp-cutting when we first appeared on TIFF.
It was the first time I did it.
It was my first original song, so I have a lot of memories.
That's right.
I did it.
I thought you were going to take a lot of pictures.
But...
I thought you were really good at dancing. Oh, but...
I was sick, but everyone was watching.
I thought there were some idols who were dancing.
I thought they were my girls.
It said that they were dancing a lot.
That's perfect.
My girls were laughing.
I think I was the most excited.
The whole concert was the last one.
It was a hot stage.
But there were so many people who came to see us.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
It was so hot at night.
Was it?
It was hot at night.
It was hot at night last year. It was hot at night. It's hot at night too. It's pretty hot at night. Last year's summer stay was like that, but isn't the heat of the night in Tokyo crazy?
It's crazy.
It's true.
There's not much wind.
I was so excited, but I was happy that everyone was excited with me.
I said that my friend was coming, but my friend said, My friend told me that she was going to see TIFF.
She said she was excited to see the show.
At that time, I was with TIFF at the S2O party event.
My friend misunderstood and said, That one? That one! I thought it was different from the idol festival, but I wonder if it was right.
I thought it was the one next door.
It was like a festival where water was flowing.
It was the same as the one next door.
I thought it was different.
It was different.
I was waiting for the to arrive at the last stage.
I was wearing a T-shirt of Mirei Hoshida and other goods.
I went to her store.
She bought a lot of goods and brought them to me.
She brought a ring to me.
I thought she was my friend, ring to my house. I told him to stop because we were friends.
I was surprised.
I thought he was wearing a star-shaped dress.
I thought he was going to the bathroom.
He was a little bit messy.
That happened.
I spent the summer like that.
It was a wonderful summer. It was a wonderful summer.
I remember a lot.
I remember.
I don't remember the August 1st.
I look back.
That's all for the Yukaide Fufu-na survey.
Next.
This is the topic.
The topic is Yukaide Fufu-na Ebi-chuu GPT.
Yes.
It's a chat GPT that's is a topic of chat GPT.
This is a service that gives you a quick answer to any questions.
We will do a chat GPT and a Ebi-chu GPT.
Please ask us any questions in the comments.
We will answer them right away.
Not just the correct answer.
I think we will answer it right away. I will answer it right away. I will answer it right away.
I will answer it right away.
If you can answer it, I will choose.
Why is it so cute?
It's because I was born with it.
What is your favorite cosmetic brand?
What is your favorite cosmetic brand? Recently...
Recently...
Vanilla Co.
Vanilla Co. is good.
I'm a big fan of Vanilla Co.
What's your annual income?
My annual income is...
35 million yen.
That's good.
What's the secret to being sexy?
It's something you have to be born with.
Of course.
Can you be a gyaru?
Of course!
I hate being a gyaru.
What should you eat tomorrow?
Cold Chinese food.
That's a good one. What did you do this summer? What should I eat? Tomorrow is cold Chinese food. Oh, that's good.
What did you do this summer?
I slept too much, so I went to the gym.
Really?
How to make Yunopi a gal.
She's a gal.
That's true.
She's a gal. Actually, she is. She is a gyaru.
She might be a gyaru.
What did you eat recently?
What did I eat recently?
Mango.
I ate a lot of pretzels.
What do you do on a sleepless night?
I sleep with my spirit.
I don't have that day.
You sleep early. I don't have that day. You sleep early.
I can resist when I grow up.
You can sleep even if you say you're going to sleep now.
I think it's really amazing.
I'm going to express my feelings now.
It's hard.
I'll definitely say it.
Long time no see.
Hello everyone. I'm Kokona Sakuragi.
It's long.
What?
Does your foot smell?
Do you want to know?
My scent is the scent of roses.
What's the highlight of the next week's release? Oh, that's right. The highlight is that summer is really packed. What did you do?
I went to the sea, went to the pool, ate watermelon and did a long-distance swimming.
That's amazing.
It's a summer set.
That's right. That's good.
I did summer.
I want you to tell me how to make work fun. Let's ask her all the questions from the beginning.
Let's do Mire-chan's consultation room.
Let's ask her.
What Korean food do you want to eat now?
Ah, I want to eat a hot-sum.
You want to eat it?
Hot-sum is really good.
I have no homework for the summer vacation.
Don't watch it.
You don't have time to watch this.
Hurry up.
I have to do it in two more times.
I forgot to say that I'm an FP.
Me too. What! Me too!
Me too?
I was also a FP.
I was busy with Yonamiya and I forgot about it until August 1st.
I had so much time to study.
I was memorizing the script so my memory is so good.
It's the worst.
It's bad, even though you have all the conditions.
I don't have time like this.
It's the worst.
You don't have time like this?
I don't have time like this.
It's bad.
Is it over?
I remembered.
It's crazy. Is it over? I just remembered. Ah, it's over. That's right.
But one year is...
Is it one year later?
It's February.
It's one year to leave the previous results as it is.
So I can still go.
It's been two years, so I can still go.
I'm bored now.
It's almost autumn.
That's all. It was a fun and happy Ebi-chu GPT.
So,
Ebi-chu's fun and happy showroom, the 72nd episode,
is ending in a flash.
There's a notice here.
There's a lot.
I wrote it on the back.
Oh, you wrote it.
Oh, this is it.
This is the announcement.
Yes, this is it.
The mid-temperature performance will be held on October 1st, Saturday at the Yagai Stage of Shichibu Music Park.
It will be at noon from 13 o 13pm, so please come and play.
We are waiting for you.
And...
Oh, this one should be played by Kokona.
Sakuragi Kokona Seidansou Live will be held at 7pm on September 17th at ZEPP Shinjuku.
Tickets are currently on sale, so please wait for us.
We are waiting for you.
And...
We have Star Dust The Party 2024.
It's a group of girls from Star Dust.
There are groups with boys in it.
There's a unit too.
The details are already announced.
We have events with various teams.
We might do unit events, but we don't know yet.
We are planning to do shuffle events.
We will have 3 events from November 22nd, 18, 23, 13 and 18.
We will have the event at Yokohama Buntaini, which we recently opened.
Please come and join us.
Yes, please.
My birthday announcement?
It was around October 30th.
I'm sorry.
October, yes.
I think it was October 30th.
I will perform at ZEPP Shinjuku.
We will do the special event.
ZEPP Shinjuku has a lot of access.
After ZEPP Shinjuku, there is also a special event for MIRAE RIZ.
It's packed, so please come.
Oh, it's here.
This year is about Halloween, so there are pictures of, so please get it.
Wow!
Let's introduce the top 5 of the final ranking.
1st place is Riku-san.
Oh, it's 5th place.
5th place is Poha-san.
Thank you.
4th place is Gami-Gami-san.
Thank you. 3rd place is Manchikan-san. Thank you! 4th place, GamiGami-san! Thank you! 3rd place, Manchikan-san!
Thank you!
2nd place, Tamami-san!
1st place, Riku-san!
Thank you!
Thank you everyone!
So, that's it for the 72nd episode of the showroom with a happy and rich Ebi-Chu.
The next episode will be back with the next show.
That's all for today.
We are Shiritu Ebisuya.
Bye bye! you